So, I click Start New Chat and I'll be able to start typing over here, you know, just
like I would with any other chatbot out there.
But we also have this option, so this is about...
Hey there, I'm co-pilot.
You can chat with me just like you would with a friend.
Feel free to ask me anything on your mind, share your ideas out loud, or even chat in another
language if you like.
And you can always tweak the sound and speed of my voice in the settings, so what's on your
mute?
So, as you see, I can click on this button to come back.
As you see, this is what we had as voice mode on chat-up-t, right?
So this is about talking to co-pilot as you see an auditory AI assistant will come up and
I'll be able to have a conversation with it, right?
So, let's do it actually.
Hey there, welcome back.
Hello, I am very, very beginning.
I sound good.
Just let me know what kind of vibe you're aiming for with the prayer, and I hope you cross
something.
I hope you stop talking when I'm talking, right?
So, I'm very beginner when it comes to French.
I know English, but I know very little French, and I want you to start teaching me, you
know?
I want to start learning French.
Just let me know when you're ready and I'm here to help out.
So, I want to practice conversation with you, right?
So, you start a beginner's conversation in French, you start co-pilot, do you hear me?
Okay, I ask her to stop talking when I'm talking and now she's not talking at all, but whatever.